<application>
  <component name="CoursesStorage">
    <courses>
      <course>
        <option name="courseMode" value="Study" />
        <option name="description" value="Cities become smarter and smarter to meet our needs. Parking spaces are an essential element of urban spaces, and you as a developer can help improve them. In this project, you will create a parking lot managing program that will keep track of vacant spots and parked cars.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://hyperskill.org&quot;&gt;https://hyperskill.org/projects/75&lt;/a&gt;" />
        <option name="humanLanguage" value="English" />
        <option name="location" value="$USER_HOME$/dev/code/Parking Lot" />
        <option name="name" value="Parking Lot" />
        <option name="programmingLanguage" value="kotlin" />
        <option name="type" value="Hyperskill" />
      </course>
      <course>
        <option name="courseMode" value="Study" />
        <option name="description" value="Privacy is an important matter is the realm of the Internet. When sending a message, you want to be sure that no-one but the addressee with the key can read it. The entirety of the modern Web is encrypted - take https for example! Don’t stay behind: hop on the encryption/decryption train and learn the essential basics while implementing this simple project.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://hyperskill.org&quot;&gt;https://hyperskill.org/projects/46&lt;/a&gt;" />
        <option name="humanLanguage" value="English" />
        <option name="location" value="$USER_HOME$/dev/code/Encryption-Decryption" />
        <option name="name" value="Encryption-Decryption" />
        <option name="programmingLanguage" value="JAVA" />
        <option name="programmingLanguageVersion" value="11" />
        <option name="type" value="Hyperskill" />
      </course>
      <course>
        <option name="courseMode" value="Study" />
        <option name="description" value="What can be better than a cup of coffee during a break? A coffee that you don’t have to make yourself. It’s enough to press a couple of buttons on the machine and you get a cup of energy; but first, we should teach the machine how to do it. In this project, you will work on programming a coffee machine simulator. The machine works with typical products: coffee, milk, sugar, and plastic cups; if it runs out of something, it shows a notification. You can get three types of coffee: espresso, cappuccino and latte. Since nothing’s for free, it also collects the money.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://hyperskill.org&quot;&gt;https://hyperskill.org/projects/33&lt;/a&gt;" />
        <option name="humanLanguage" value="English" />
        <option name="location" value="$USER_HOME$/dev/code/Coffee Machine" />
        <option name="name" value="Coffee Machine" />
        <option name="programmingLanguage" value="JAVA" />
        <option name="programmingLanguageVersion" value="11" />
        <option name="type" value="Hyperskill" />
      </course>
      <course>
        <option name="courseMode" value="Study" />
        <option name="description" value="Blockchains are data structures where blocks are inseparably connected. What makes blockchains so special is the security level they offer due to the way they are constructed. Blockchains are unhackable, so it makes perfect sense why cryptocurrency makes use of this technology. In this project, you will try yourself at making a microcosm where virtual miners earn cryptocurrency and exchange messages and transactions using blockchain. As difficult as the project might be, it is bound to pay off: not in cryptocurrency, but in knowledge and skills.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://hyperskill.org&quot;&gt;https://hyperskill.org/projects/50&lt;/a&gt;" />
        <option name="humanLanguage" value="English" />
        <option name="location" value="$USER_HOME$/dev/code/Blockchain" />
        <option name="name" value="Blockchain" />
        <option name="programmingLanguage" value="JAVA" />
        <option name="programmingLanguageVersion" value="11" />
        <option name="type" value="Hyperskill" />
      </course>
    </courses>
  </component>
</application>